To reinforce how inheritance works,
为了强调继承的原理
I've added an example to the Gaussian class code.
我在 Gaussian 类中添加了一个继承示例
I've written a new Python class called distribution.
我编写了一个新的 Python 类 叫做 Distribution
This class is going to be the parent class of
该类将是
both the Gaussian class and
Gaussian 类以及
the binomial class that you're going to code at the end of the lesson.
你将在课程结束时编写的 Binomial 类的父类
A lot of the codes should look familiar.
代码看起来应该不陌生
The init function was the same as the Gaussian init.
比如 init 函数和 Gaussian init 一样
I've simplified the read data file function so that it only reads in a data set,
我简化了 read_data_file 函数 使其仅读取数据集
whereas before this function also calculated the mean and standard deviation of the data.
而之前该函数还会计算数据的均值和标准偏差
The Gaussian class code has changed slightly.
Gaussian 类的代码有微小的变化
Now the Gaussian class inherits from the distribution class.
现在 Gaussian 类继承自 Distribution 类
The init function uses the distributions init function.
init 函数使用 Distribution 的 init 函数
Scrolling down the read data file method is still in the Gaussian class.
向下滚动会发现 read_data_file 方法依然位于 Gaussian 类中
This is because I wanted to override the read data file method from
因为我想重写 Distribution 类的 read_data_file 方法
the distribution class in order to calculate the mean and standard deviation.
以便计算均值和标准偏差
Even though the code looks a little bit different than before,
虽然代码看起来和之前有所不同
the Gaussian class works exactly the same way as it did before.
但是 Gaussian 类的工作原理完全一样
It might seem like the changes in the code are superficial and I'd agree with that.
似乎代码变化多此一举 我也这么认为
I mostly wanted to introduce inheritance so that you could recognize the syntax.
但是我只是想引入继承代码 使你能熟悉语法
Near the end of the lesson,
在这节课快结束时
we're going to look at the source code for scikit-learn.
我们将查看 scikit-learn 的源代码
A package like scikit-learn contains many classes that use inheritance.
像 scikit-learn 这样的软件包里面有很多继承类
You'll have an easier time understanding
现在你已经明白继承的原理
the syntax now that you've seen how inheritance works.
应该更容易理解语法
I've provided this distribution and
我在下一部分提供了 Distribution 和 Gaussian 类的代码
Gaussian code for you in the next section so that you can play around with it.
使你能够自己探索这些代码
We're getting close to the end of the lesson,
这节课就快结束了
the next step is to modularize all of this code into
下一步是将所有代码模块化成单独的 Python 文件
separate Python files then you will see how to make a Python package.
然后你将学习如何创建 Python 软件包
The last steps will include extending the code to include
最后的步骤将包括扩展代码
a binomial distribution and uploading the code to Pi Pi.
从而包含二项分布并将代码上传到 PyPI
So, let's start by modularizing this code.
我们开始模块化代码吧